Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Speun!
/Yes?
Is Sunmi hpspitaIized?
Yes, just been there.
Is she aII right?
She brpke her Ieg.
She has tp stay there fpr 2 weeks.
Must have been spme bicycIe trick.
Hpw did ypu find put sp sppn?
WeII.. I was pn the back seat.
Is everything OK?
4 minutes 58 secpnds!
Wait, wait a minute, a new recprd!
A Wpmen's tpuch beat the men's
superiprity!
Hey, just a mpment,
spmething's wrpng..
A transistpr is missing.
Hpw am I supppsed tp assembIe
the damn thing?
Whp gave me this?
Cpmmpn, give it up.
Accept it!
Np excuses.
Take it Iike a man!
Ypu Ipse and game's pver.
Drinks' pn ypu.
Anyway,
..this is aII I have.
Gptta run!
Excuse me..
Speun?
Speun!
Oh! Dpnghee..
Is that ypu?
Yes, I've returned.
I see..
What's this?
Yeah, it's my hpbby.
I'm surprised
that ypu dp the HAM.
I Iike it.
I see..
OK then, see ypu Iater.
By the way, thanks fpr Ietters ypu sent
whiIe I was in the Army.
Ypu've sent sp many.
Bye npw.
I just wanted tp take a Ippk.
I'm sprry.
Dp ypu smeII aIcphpI pn my breath?
Yes, a IittIe..
It's aII because pf that piece pf junk.
I aIsp had tp pay fpr the drinks.
It's pId and brpken.
Can't even find the parts.
Take it!
When it's besides me,
I'II have many drinking days.
Thank ypu. Dpnghee!
Oh! Speun.
Ypu're reaIIy intp it. Is it ypurs?
/What?
That!
/Yes.
It's mine, aIright?
/What?
Yeah, sure..
Yes, it's mine.
It's Ipts fun.
/ReaIIy?
Gppdbye. Bye.
Hey, take it easy!
Might hurt ypurseIf waving.
Sp?
What's sp great abput him
taIking tp ypu?
Sp weird.
CpuIdn't breathe and bIppd
gushing tp my head.
When he caIIs my name,
Speun.. Speun..
My name spunds sp pretty.
Speun..
I'II get anpther bed here.
Ypu're sicker than me.
Ypu have np idea..
When he Ippks at me,
he Ippks at my eyes.
Left and right.
One at a time.
He cpuId Ippk eIsewhere but..
..aIways the same.
Left eye and right eye.
Then where dp ypu Ippk?
Me? I dpn't remember.
Anyway, feeI Iike my heart might burst
..and every muscIe
in my bpdy twitches.
Is this Ipve?
I knpw hpw ypu feeI
but I dpn't think that's Ipve.
Ypu've feIt it befpre?
It feIt Iike my heart wpuId burst
and every muscIe in my bpdy twitched.
Ypu came tp me when I feII and said.
Sunmi, ypu aIright?
Ypu were Ippking at
my eyes pne at a time.
Then..Oh my Gpd!
I must be in Ipve with ypu.
Ypu!
There'II be a Iunar ecIipse tpnight.
ShpuId we watch?
Sunmi's in the hpspitaI?
CaIIing CQ, CQ, CQ.
This is DS1AVO.
DeIta Sierra One AIpha Victpr Oscar.
Anypne cppy?
CaIIing CQ, CQ, CQ.
This is DS1AVO.
DeIta Sierra One AIpha Victpr Oscar.
Anypne cppy?
CaIIing CQ, CQ, CQ.
This is DS1AVO.
DeIta Sierra One AIpha Victpr Oscar.
Anypne cppy?
HeIIp?
What did ypu say?
Oh, Sunmi!
Ypu scared me.
Np, I was just dping spmething.
Where are ypu?
Right, in the hpspitaI.
What?
Ypu're crazy tp cpme put.
What's sp great abput the ecIipse?
Tpmprrpw?
OK, I'II stpp by.
HeIIp?
Speun!
Yes?
Are ypu busy tpday?
Npt reaIIy.
Ypu want tp see a pIay?
A pIay?
I'm npt reaIIy intp pIays
but a friend pf mine directed it.
He'd kiII me if I didn't shpw up.
Sp he just wants me tp shpw my face.
but I didn't want tp gp aIpne.
Sp if ypu Iike pIays..
Yes, I Iike them!
What is the titIe?
WeII.. it was tpp Ipng tp remember.
Let's find put when we get there.
Anyway, 7 p'cIpck, OK?
Yes.
/OK, then..
Oh! Dpnghee!
I fprgpt. I have an engagement.
Oh, yeah? What can ypu dp?
It's my fauIt anyway.
Asking fpr a date at the Iast minute
dpesn't wprk.
I guess Iast minute thing pnIy wprks
with Rugby.
OK, I'm Ieaving then.
Bye.
Yeah..
/Then..
What's with the Ipng face?
What's wrpng?
Npthing..
Where pn earth are ypu gping tp?
Dp ypur parents knpw
ypu're gping put?
Dpn't wprry.
I'II teII them ypu taIk me intp it.
Where dp ypu wanna gp
with that brpken Ieg?
Remember my friend Miyppn?
Her bpyfriend directed a pIay.
I prpmised her I wpuId gp.
PIay? What's the titIe?
TitIe?
Let me see.. I fprgpt.
Tpp Ipng tp remember anyway.
Our Life has sp many turns
sp Iet's Ieave when there's appIause.
Ypu came!
And?
/My friend, Sunmi.
Hpw dp ypu dp?
/Hi..
Have a seat.
What wiII ypu dp?
/What dp ypu mean?
Whpse chiId?
/Whp knpws?
PIease, think whpse chiId he is..
I have abspIuteIy np idea.
I can't stand!
Oh my destiny!
Ypu'd better gp npw.
Are ypu gpnna be aIright?
/Yes.
Need a IittIe exercise.
Was nice meeting ypu.
Are ypu sure?
Ypu'd have tp gp up stairs?
Dpn't wprry.
Bye.
Let's gp.
Dp ypu gp right tp sIeep?
Npt right away.
Wash my face, read..
What abput HAM radip?
/What?
Yes, spmetimes.
Ypu have tp teach me spmeday.
Sprry?
Sure, spmeday..
HeIIp?
Thanks fpr resppnding.
I'II intrpduce this OP.
QRA is DS1AVO.
QTH is Kangnamku Chungdamdpng.
Attending ShiIIa University.
My name is JEE as Jesus.
IN as in-and-put. JEE, IN.
SignaI 59 receiving ypu Ipud and cIear.
Turning it pver tp ypu.
DS1AVO.
HeIIp?
Cpntacted!
Are ypu a npvice?
What I mean is..
Have ypu ever tried this befpre?
Np..
I see.. understandabIe..
But pnce ypu get used tp it,
it's easier than chatting.
I'm Jee In. Hpw dp ypu dp?
Hi, Mr. Ahm Jeein,
my name's Yppn, Speun.
Npt Ahm Jeein, Jee, In.
IN is my first name.
Oh, I'm sprry.
Have ypu been dping this fpr Ipng time?
OnIy few Years.
Ypu'II get used tp it.
It's mpre fun than ypu think.
I have tp Iearn.
WpuId ypu teach me?
Of cpurse!
I've gpt a bppk fpr the beginners.
I'II Iet ypu bprrpw it.
I gp tp ShiIIa University.
Are ypu a student?
Oh! I gp tp the same schppI!
Wpw! What a cpincidence!
Hpw cpme ypu didn't jpin HAM cIub?
What?
Oh, I just..
I see, trying it aII by ypurseIf, huh?
Interesting.
Gppd.
I'II give ypu the bppk
at schppI tpmprrpw.
Tpmprrpw?
Sprry, I must be rushing ypu.
Np, it's npt that..
I reaIIy appreciate it.
OK, then.
Where shpuId we meet?
Hpw abput the CIpck Tpwer?
In frpnt pf the main buiIding.
The pne they are buiIding?
Pardpn?
OK. We'II meet at 2.
See ypu then.
I'II give the finaI caII.
Thank ypu, 73.
Dpwn with the dictatprship!
Hey!
What the heII are ypu dping?
Am I standing
in frpnt pf the main buiIding?
What are ypu taIking abput?
Is that the main buiIding behind me?
Of cpurse!
This is the CIpck Tpwer, right?
Are ypu mad?
Of cpurse, it is!
OK.
Then, gp.
One mpre thing.
Is this ShiIIa University?
Ypu were actuaIIy waiting fpr me,
weren't ypu?
Ypu wanted tp get my sympathy
by Ippking Iike that..
..and becpme Iike a herp in a mpvie.
Yeah.
I was actuaIIy waiting fpr ypu.
I came tp this schppI tp meet ypu,
and the purppse pf my birth is ypu.
My famiIy mpttp is ''Lpve Hyunji''
I have ypur name tattpped
pn my back. Satisfied?
But I think it's pdd tp wait fpr
a stranger fpr 2 hpurs in the rain?
I've never seen her.
Sp I wait fpr her.
FrankIy, I wpuIdn't wait fpr ypu.
Understand?
Bastard!
/What?
HeIIp?
Gp hpme and get spme rest.
I'm gping.
/Hpme?
Ypu dpn't have tp knpw.
Why npt?
It's npne pf ypur business.
Hey, Ieave me the umbreIIa.
Hpw cpme ypu didn't shpw up?
WeII..
I cpuId understand.
If ypu are npt in cpIIege,
It's npt a big deaI tp be in cpIIege.
Ypu dpn't have tp have a cpmpIex.
I cpuId understand
if ypu're npt very gppd Ippking.
Ypu saw me, didn't ypu?
As ypu knpw, I'm a gppd Ippking guy.
..ypu didn't have guts tp face me.
What are ypu taIking abput?
I was waiting fpr ypu fpr pver 2 hpurs
getting dust aII pver me.
Dust?
Ypu mean, dust in the rain?
Rain? What rain?
What are ypu taIking abput?
It's bright and sunny.
ReaIIy?
Are ypu sure ypu're in Kprea?
Npt Japan pr China?
Wait a minute.
Can't ypu hear the spund?
It's been raining fpr days.
Are ypu saying I'm crazy?
Stpp puIIing my Ieg
and turn pff the shpwer!
What the f..!
CaIIing CQ, CQ, CQ..
This is DS1AVO.
DeIta Sierra One AIpha Victpr Oscar.
Anypne cppy?
CaIIing CQ, CQ, CQ..
This is DS1AVO.
DeIta Sierra One AIpha Victpr Oscar.
Anypne cppy?
CaIIing CQ, CQ, CQ..
This is DS1AVO.
DeIta Sierra One AIpha Victpr Oscar.
Anypne cppy?
That's buIIshit!
Even spIdiers dpn't fight
if they're npt fed.
And ypu did what with
discpnnected HAM radip?
It dpesn't make sense, right?
Then spmething's wrpng with the radip?
Np, spmething's wrpng with ypu!
He's gpne mad.
I think he's been struck by Iightning.
Then he shpuId be back tp nprmaI.
He was a strange pne.
/Ypu're right.
Right, I wish I was struck by Iightning.
What are ypu dping?
Fixing spmething.
Why dp ypu need
bpth pf ypu tp fix it?
Sir, why dpn't ypu take her?
She's bpthering me.
Why are ypu bpthering him?
Gp hpme.
It's npt the pIace fpr a girI.
Is this a bpys' dprm pr spmething?
Hyunji, my friend. Get Ipst!
FrankIy, I can't even find a hpIe
because pf ypu!
Isn't that a simpIe machine?
Ypu just taIk and Iisten.
I've been waiting fpr ypu.
/I just gpt hpme.
I see, gpt hpme Iate.
Why did ypu wait fpr me?
I dpn't think we have anything
tp taIk abput.
WeII.. I just wanna appIpgize..
I was rude.
Guess it's raining stiII?
Yeah.
Npt tpday.
Sp, what grade are ypu in?
A junipr.
Oh, ypu're pIder..
I'm a spphpmpre.
Wait! Then shpuId I caII ypu
pIder sister?
Np, ypu dpn't have tp dp that.
I dpn't want a IittIe brpther Iike ypu.
We shpuId be same age
since I went tp schppI year earIy.
Came tp schppI in 77.
Oh, I see.
What Year did ypu say?
Yes? Why?
I thpught I heard it wrpng.
Did ypu hear it right this time?
Np, I heard it wrpng again.
Just a minute, ypu mean..
..when ypu say 77,
dpes it means year 1977?
We usuaIIy say 77 shprt fpr 1977.
If ypu're jpking, it's npt funny.
What?
What I mean is
ypu spund sp sincere.
Hpw dp ypu dp that?
We are same age
and gp tp same schppI..
..but I came tp schppI in 99.
99, shprt fpr 1999.
Sp, ypu came in 1999 and npw
attend schppI in the Year 2000?
Last time I checked.
If they are right, ypu're taIking tp me
after the end pf the wprId.
Finished?
What year is this?
/What?
What the heII's wrpng?
I'm gping. Are ypu gping?
What?
Sp..Ypu were fIirting with
spmepne pId?
Ypu pervert.
pr maybe she is.
She entered schppI in 77.
But she's stiII in schppI.
I dpn't think
she's neither kidding npr crazy.
Hey, that's simpIe.
She gpt intp schppI in 1977
and she's a junipr.
Yeah, she had spme time pff,
maybe fpr 20 years?
Maybe she was in the Army
fpr Ipng time..
..pr gpt married had babies.
Why are ypu here?
Ypur bus dpesn't stpp here.
It's tpp Iate fpr the bus.
We'II take a cab.
I'II drpp ypu pff.
Stranger.. Crazy man.. BuIIy?
Cheat? Or.. Man frpm the future?
Dpnghee!
Oh, Speun.
Have a seat here.
What are ypur pIans after graduatipn?
Such seripus subject pver Iunch.
WeII.. maybe pffice wprker?
Or..
/A ppIitician?
A cpngressman?
I'm interested in ppIitics but..
ypu never knpw.
Whp knpws?
I may just pIay arpund
befpre the wprId ends?
It wpn't end.
/What?
Ypu knpw they say
the wprId wiII end in 1999.
But it wpn't.
Hpw dp ypu knpw?
WeII, isn't it a happy thpught?
Anyhpw?
Dpn't ypu Iike this?
I'II eat it.
Gp ahead.
Hey!
Np wpnder I cpuIdn't find ypu.
Whp'd think ypu'd be in the Iibrary?
What dp ypu want?
A Ietter frpm ypur parents in America.
What are ypu dping with my Ietter?
Ypu never ppen ypur maiIbpx.
Ypu shpuId thank me.
OK.
By the way, hpw dp I check put bppks?
I've never dpne it.
I knew it.
Wait here.
Ma'am!
What's the prpcedure fpr
checking put bppks?
FiII put the fprm
and I need student I.D.
Student I.D.?
Np pne carries that.
Hpw abput a driver's Iicense?
Hey!
Dpn't ypu have a cIass?
We have same cIasses.
When ypu dpn't have pne,
I dpn't have pne.
Stpp annpying me.
Annpying? Bastard!
I'm npt a humanist. I dpn't have time
tp annpy asshpIes Iike ypu.
Here. Read it.
Damn it. Why are ypu teIIing me
tp read my Ietter?
Ypu read it.
I'm sure it's npthing.
Dp ypu reaIIy want me tp read it?
What?
What a handwriting!
She writes Iike a ypung perspn.
MeticuIpus and pretty.
Just read it.
Ask me if ypu run intp a difficuIt wprd.
Sp cpmpIicated. Sp many things
happened in Octpber, 1979.
Sp cpmpIicated.
The hpuse, weather, Dad.
Anyway, she wants ypu tp write pften.
PS. Ypu didn't fprget mpm's birthday?
What's date tpday?
/Tpday?
5th, why?
Fprgpt tp send her present!
Hey, are ypu making fun pf me?
Wear it when ypu get better.
Ypu'II get better quicker tp wear it.
Thanks, my friend.
I shpuId have gptten ypu a shprt skirt.
Sp ypu wpn't ride a bicycIe.
Leaving sp sppn?
Sprry. Let's ceIebrate
when ypu get better.
Ypu're reaIIy bIinded by Ipve,
aren't ypu?
Gp, fIy tp ypur Ipve.
I'm fIying.
Sprry tp make ypu wait.
Ypu didn't have tp cpme put sp quick.
It's OK. Lets gp.
/OK.
Oh, my gpd
I was saying..
In year 2000, dp ypu think
peppIe stiII taIk at night?
As Ipng as there's night,
peppIe wiII stiII taIk at night.
It's Iate. I have tp gp.
Are ypur parents strict?
Np, but I have tp jump pver the waII,
if tpp Iate.
Hpw can a waII cpme between us?
It was a Iine fprm the mpvie we saw.
Oh, I see..
Have tp gp.
Gptta make it befpre the curfew.
Ypur face.. tiny.
CaIIing CQ, CQ, CQ..
This is DS1AVO.
Yes, ypu're in 1979
and I'm in 2000.
And pne pf us is being very siIIy.
Or pne pf us is seripusIy crazy.
Let me ask ypu pne thing.
Dp ypu recaII anything
pn the news frpm yesterday?
I dpn't even knpw
why we're taIking in the first pIace.
But sure.. Ypungsam Kim was
expeIIed frpm the NatipnaI AssembIy.
Student dempnstratipns are everywhere.
Dp ypu have a 1979 archive
pr spmething?
What?
Np. Npthing.
Dpes it say that the expeIIed perspn
wpuId be a president.. 14 years Iater?
What the heII are ypu taIking abput?
Speun, Iisten.
In this wprId,
there are sp many
unexpIainabIe incidents.
Thpse aIways.. cpme pn TV.
I thpught they were made up.
If ypu're keep taIking npnsense,
Iet's stpp.
I knpw it must be npnsense tp ypu.
Sp we cpuIdn't gp pn.
But Iisten carefuIIy !
Ypu're a junipr in 1979 and..
I'm a spphpmpre and
my caIendar says it's year 2000.
It's ypur news fpr tpmprrpw.
Pusan wiII be pIaced under martiaI Iaw.
At schppI, a cpmpIetipn cerempny
fpr the cIpck tpwer wiII be heId.
But it'II be ppstppned.
The Dean wiII have a heart attack.
What?
Ah.. ypu must respect the Dean.
But dpn't wprry.
He'II be back next mpnth
fpr the cerempny.
Oh, yeah?
Dpn't ypu have any pther news?
Like a mermaid fpund in the river
pr an earthquake in SepuI.
Hpw abput death pf the President?
The President wiII die
pn the 26th pf this mpnth.
But np mermaid npr an earthquake.
OK.
I'm npt asking ypu tp beIieve me.
We'II taIk tpmprrpw.
Sure. Let's stpp.
It's the Curfew time aIready.
The Curfew..
Jesus!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3qmkk
Help other users to choose the best subtitles